就这样在分开六个月之后
And so, after six months apart,
莉莉阿姨和马修叔叔 终于重修旧好了
Aunt Lily and Uncle Marshall were finally back together.
天那
Oh, my God.
这些煎饼太好吃了
These pancakes are delicious!
谢谢
Yes. Thank you.
你不在的这个夏天 我学会了做饭
Um, I learned how to cook while you were gone this summer.
那今晚你来做饭吧
Oh. Do you want to cook dinner tonight?
好啊
Yeah, sure.
煎饼如何
How about pancakes?
一切恢复了正常 几乎是...
And things were back to normal... almost.
也许你没有太多的灶具 但至少我嫁了个
You may not have much range, but at least I'm marrying a guy
会烧煎饼的男人
who knows how to make pancakes.
Oh, um...
我意思是...
I mean, um...
我知道我们俩还没讨论
Well, I... I realize that we haven't really discussed
我们和好是不是意味 我们要结婚
whether us getting back together means us getting married, but...
但我仍然想结
I still wanna.
你还想结吗?
Do you still wanna?
真的吗?
Really?
当然了　我爱你
Of course, I love you.
等等  你就这么向我求婚?
No, I mean, that's how you're gonna do it?
就句　你还想结婚? 这是我听过的最寒碜的求婚
"Do you still wanna?" That's like the lamest proposal ever.
当我向你求婚的时候 我单膝跪下　也许我会说
When I did it, I got down on my knees... I don't know, I'm just saying.
马修・埃里克森 你愿意...
Marshall Eriksen, will you ma...
- 不行　不行 - 怎么啦
- No, no, no, no, no, no. - What?!
你不能这么开门见山 要循序渐进
You can't lead with that. You got to... build up to that.
你要先来个演讲暖场
You got to have, like, a little speech.
你还记得你是怎么向我求婚的
Do you remember your proposal to me?
我确实准备了一篇演讲
I had a speech prepared.
那你想听什么呢
What do you want to hear?
我不知道　也许 你可以说
I don't know. I mean, you could tell me,
比如说　你可以讲讲我有多帅 我既幽默又聪明
like, about how good-looking and funny and smart I am
我后来有一段时间有健身
and I've been working out lately.
如果你能提到这个就更好了
It might be nice for you to mention something... about that.
马修...
Marshall...
- 你太帅了... - 谢谢
- you are good-looking... - Thank you.
- 你又幽默 - 谢谢
- You're funny. - Oh, thanks.
- 又聪明 - 你不妨再掉几滴眼泪
- You're smart. - And a few tears wouldn't hurt.
你他妈的就不能跟我结婚吗?
Okay, would you freakin' marry me already?
我当然会和你结婚了
I'll marry you. Of course.
在我把戒指带上以前 别指望我会跟你上床?
But, um, until you see a ring on this finger, don't expect me to put out.
好的
Yeah, right.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第八集
Transcript : Raceman Subtitles : Willow's Team
翻译：    雨亦奇       校对：    silver
www.forom.com
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
我会给你这个
I'll give you this.
这是个糖浆的妙用
That was a very creative use of syrup.
我现在甚至不能直视Mrs Butterworth (一种糖浆)
I can't even look Mrs. Butterworth in the eye.
天那　我们要结婚了
Oh, my God. We're getting married!
我知道　我知道
I know, I know.
先是一阵幸福
It was a moment of happiness,
紧接着　却是一阵恐慌
followed of course by a moment of total panic.
知道吗　莉莉阿姨 第一次取消婚礼
See, when they called off their first wedding,
然后只身去了旧金山
Aunt Lily took off for San Francisco
留下马修叔叔和一大堆烂摊子
leaving Uncle Marshall with the unfortunate task
他得去跟他的整个家族解释
of telling his entire family.
是　她走了 婚礼也取消了
Yeah, so now she's gone and the wedding's off.
这种自己一走了之  不管后果 的人你们管他叫什么?
What do you call someone who just takes off and leaves like that?
你管她叫什么
What do you call that?
这会不会有点过啦
I think that that's a little strong.
我真不敢相信你会用这个词
I can't even believe you would use a word like that.
天那　奶奶
Geez, Grandma.
我取消婚礼把事情搞得一团糟 对吧
Man, I made a big mess by canceling this wedding, didn't I?
不要紧　宝贝
It's okay, baby.
不过你不是 现在才意识到吧?
You're not just realizing that now, are you?
一想到要站在一群
God, the idea of standing up there in front of all those people
讨厌我的人前面...
who hate my guts...
就让我有马上跑到 大西洋城结婚的冲动
just makes me want to run off to Atlantic City and get married today.
对啊
Yeah.
11点新闻 东河里还有食人鱼?
Coming up at 11:00: Are there piranhas in the East River?
无知能让你被吃掉
What you don't know... could eat you.
罗宾　停一下
Robin! Stop the news!
- 怎么啦? - 没事　他们是我的朋友
- What the hell? - It's okay. They're my friends.
我们要去大西洋城结婚 你跟我们一起去吧
We're going to Atlantic City to elope. You got to come with us.
天那　太棒了
Oh, my God, that is so fantastic!
我不知道我现在能不能走
I-I don't know if I can just leave work.
好了　今晚就让 迈克来播新闻好了
It's  okay; Mike can read the news tonight.
迈克　你识字吧?
Hey, Mike... you can read, right?
我朗读最在行了
Yeah, I'm the best at reading.
- 让我们一起大西洋城吧 - 走
- Let's go to Atlantic City! - Yeah!
你们俩要私奔　这太棒了
You guys are eloping! Oh, that's fantastic.
你这样作是不是因为 罗嗦的泰德叔叔总有一天会知道?
Wait, is this because there's a time crunch Uncle Ted should know about?
我不希望... 因为我们要喝醉了去结婚
I hope not because I plan on getting hammered.
哥们　这听起很有意思 但我手头工作放不下...
Guys, this sounds like so much fun, but I can't really take off work.
我现在有点重要 我是项目经理
I'm kind of important around here, you know? I'm the project manager.
泰德　在以后
Ted, for the rest of our lives,
我们都会一直传说着
we are going to be telling the amazing story
我们怎么去大西洋城结婚的故事
of how we went to Atlantic City and got married.
你不想出现在这个故事里吗
Don't you want to be in that story?
我当然想了
Of course I do.
- 让我们一起去吧 - 好的
- Let's go to Atlantic City! - Yeah!
但是以后说起这个故事的时候 能不能把我刚才犹豫这部分省略掉
Oh, but when we tell the story, can you leave out the part where I hesitate?
没问题
You got it.
嘿　哥们
Hey, guys.
哇　足浴啊
Wow. A pedicure.
如果一个男人 去足浴有什么不妥的话
Uh, if there were any shame in a dude getting a pedicure
我觉得也不至于 成为男性杂志上的特写
I don't think there would have been a feature about it in Details magazine.
我们现在要去大西洋城结婚
We're going to Atlantic City to elope right now!
莉莉　恭喜你
Oh, congratulations, Lily.
马修　你要结婚? 你有什么毛病啊?
Marshall, you're getting married? What the hell?
去还是不去?
So are you in or not?
开玩笑 我当然要去
Hell, yeah, I'm in!
但　等等　我快好了
Just... I'm almost done.
- 没关系　我们也来... - 实际上　我意思是...
- No, we got to get going to the... - Well, actually, I mean...
今天是我结婚的日子 既然我们在这了
It is my wedding day, and since we're here...
那我们也先做个足浴 然后才去了
So we all got a pedicure and then headed down...
大西洋城
to Atlantic City.
看这地方
Wow. Look at this place.
我想我会挑些旧的
I guess I'll have my pick of something old.
还有蓝色的... 真该有人过来给检查一下这位女士
And something blue. Somebody should really check on this lady.
大西洋城的生意一直在衰退
Ah, A.C., always in decline,
但绝不会崩溃
never hitting bottom.
老朋友 我又回来了
It's good to be back, old friend.
你以前来过这?
You been here before?
恩　一两次
Oh, uh, once or twice.
巴尼!
Barney!
很高兴又见到你
Ah, good to see you, too.
可能是三次
Three times, maybe.
婚礼小教堂就在那
The wedding chapel-- this is it.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready to do this?
好了
I'm ready.
- 我们去结婚吧 - 好
- Let's get married. - Yeah.
糟了　我没面纱
Oh, crap. I don't have a veil.
我是个新娘 我不能没面纱就结婚
I'm a bride; I can't get married without a veil.
还有花束 我需要面纱和花束
And a bouquet. I need a veil and a bouquet.
我们马上要结婚了
Oh, my God, we're getting married.
不要担心　放松 我马上给你找面纱
Don't  worry. Relax. We'll get you a veil, honey.
罗宾　你这件礼服真漂亮
Oh, Robin, that's a really cute outfit.
真的? 谢谢
Oh, really? Thanks.
是的　但你不能穿 我是新娘　你不能比我漂亮
Yeah, it has to go. I'm the bride; you can't look better than me.
好
Done.
我们去找花束 你们男人去找面纱
I'm going to get the bouquet. You guys get the veil.
20分钟后我们在小礼堂见
We'll meet in the chapel in 20 minutes.
走　分头行动
Ready, break.
你们想要赌一把吗
You  guys want to go gamble?
不　我们要去找面纱
No, we got to go get the veil.
或者我们说　我们找遍了 但找不到
Or we looked everywhere, and we couldn't find one.
好主意
Yeah, okay.
你们去赌吧 我去找面纱
No, you guys go ahead. I'm going to find the veil.
你就这样过? 这可是你最后20分钟的单身生活了
So this is it, right? The last 20 minutes of your single life.
- 哥们　我为你自豪 - 谢谢
- I'm proud of you, buddy. - Thanks.
- 你感觉如何? - 很好　有点紧张
- How are you feeling? - Great, a little nervous.
- 是吗? 想便便? - 不是那种紧张
- Yeah? Craps? - Not that nervous.
- 不是　我意思是你想玩骰子吗 - 当然了
- No, I mean do you want to play craps. - Oh, yeah, definitely.
好　我找到面纱了
Okay, I got the veil.
她还没做好准备要结婚
She wasn't ready to be married.
现在我们讨论下单身派对
All right, let's talk bachelor party.
你们是想要看全套脱衣舞? 还是我们开个房间
Are we thinking full-on strip club, or should we rent a room
开个私家"用具"展览会
and have a private toy show-- whew.
你刚才说什么来着?
What did you just say?
- 巴尼　不行 - 马修　我是你的伴郎
- Barney, no. - Marshall, I'm your best man.
- 你不是我的伴郎 - 我才是
- You're not my best man. - Right here.
作为伴郎 我要 给你开个单身派对
And as your best man, I have to throw you a bachelor party.
这就是好朋友要做的事
That's part of being a best friend.
- 你不是我最好的朋友 - 我才是
- You're not my best friend. - Right here.
巴尼　我没时间开单身派对
Barney, I don't have any time for a bachelor party.
我只有大概18分钟
I've got, like, 18 minutes.
18分钟
18 minutes.
你找到面纱了吗
Oh, good. Did you get the veil?
当然了
Of course.
正好花了我们18分钟
And it took us exactly 18 minutes.
我们去了脱衣舞俱乐部
We went to a strip club.
- 哥们 - 难以置信
- Dude! - Unbelievable!
我们在那时间很短 这并不是说我没有时间
We weren't there for very long. It's not like I had time
让人坐我大腿上跳舞 有人已经在我腿上跳过了
to have a lap dance or anything. I got a lap dance.
- 这是你最后一次跳这样的舞了 - 对...
- Your last lap dance ever. - Right...
什么?
What?
好　我来了
Okay, I'm here. Right?
人们来大西洋城烧钱 不就是为这个
Oh, God, the things people waste money on in Atlantic City.
我好像闻到 脱衣舞娘的味道了
Does it smell like strippers in here?
有点怪　对吧
That's weird, right?
马修和莉莉要结婚了
Marshall and Lily are getting married!
对　看这个东西
Hell, yeah, look at this.
宝贝　就是这个
Oh, baby, this is it.
- 让我们开始吧 - 好的
- Let's do this thing. - All right.
我们是来这结婚的
Hi. We're here to get married.
恭喜你 我们提供各种服务
Congratulations. We offer a variety of packages
让你实现你梦想中 这个特殊时刻
to give you the special day you've always dreamed about.
我们不需要这些 一个最简单快捷的婚礼就可以了
We don't want any of that. Just your basic quickie wedding will be fine.
对
Yeah.
你知道吗 这里不是拉斯维加斯
You know this isn't Vegas, right?
那当然　在拉斯维加斯 空气里都弥漫着赌场的味道
Well, sure. In Vegas, the casinos pump in oxygen.
这里大家除了自己 什么都没带
Here, it looks like everyone brought their own.
什么?
What?
在新泽西办个 结婚证最快要三天
It also takes three days to get a marriage license in New Jersey.
你们能登记到的 最早也要星期一
The earliest I could book you for is Monday.
不行　不行 必须是今天　这才有意思
No, no, no, it has to be today. That's the whole point.
我不知道该怎么说好
Look, I don't know what to say,
但如果你们不定星期一
but if you guys don't want to book a wedding for Monday
或者不玩把基诺 我就没法帮你
or play a round of keno, I can't help you.
三十五号
Thirty-five.
等等　我搞不懂 人们随时都可以在大西洋城结婚的
Wait, I don't understand, people get married in Atlantic City all the time.
是的　但他们不是私奔
Yes, they do, but they don't elope.
他们选择大西洋城 因为这里有白色的沙滩
They choose Atlantic City for its white sand beaches,
世界级的高档度假设施 和有异国情调的海滨
world-class amenities, and exotic Riviera feel.
你去过外面吗?
Have you been outside?
离遮阳伞不到20英尺的地方 有只腐烂了一半的虎鲸
There is half an orca whale rotting not 20 feet from the cabana.
哥们　放松点
You guys, take it easy, guys.
你确定?
Are you sure about this?
这个小礼堂所在州的婚姻法?
About the marriage laws of the state where I work in a wedding chapel?
是的　我很确定
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
往好处想 单身派对可以继续了
Bright side: the bachelor party continues!
对
Yes!
继续吗?你是说"开始" 他是说"开始"
Continues? You mean "start." He means "start."
我们去过脱衣舞俱乐部了
We went to a strip club.
二十七号
Twenty-seven.
有没有别的方法 让我们今天拿到结婚证
Is there any way that we could get a license today?
你可以去法院
You could go to the courthouse.
在特殊情况下 等待时间可以取消
In some extreme circumstances, the waiting period can be waived,
但你必须有足够的理由
but you have to have a good reason.
我们深爱对方
Well, we're in love.
还有比这更好的理由吗
What better reason could there be?
我最近听到的一个是
The last one I heard was,
我明天就要去伊拉克 保卫我们的国家
"I'm going to Iraq tomorrow to defend my country,"
但是你可以去试试
but, you know, give yours a whirl.
于是我们去了法庭...
So we went to the courthouse.
我觉得要等到天荒地老一样
God, this is taking forever.
我不敢相信他们要结婚了
Can't believe they're getting married.
我知道
I know.
我为他们感到骄傲 他们在一起经历了这么多
I am so proud of these two. After all they've been through.
事实上 那条疯狂之路
In fact, that crazy road has led them
直接把他们带到了大西洋城
all the way here to Atlantic City.
泰德　抬头
Ted, up here.
你一直盯着我衣服上的胸部看
You were just staring at my shirt boobs.
我没有
No! I wasn't.
我...是在看这件 衣服下面的美女
I-I was checking out the hot bod underneath the shirt.
好了　也许 我是在看你的衣服
Okay, look, maybe I was looking at your shirt,
但...这衣服很有意思
but it's a, it's a funny, funny shirt.
嘿　是巴尼!
Hey, it's Barney!
- 巴尼 - 你好
- Barney! - Hi.
...穿上西装
...suit up.
...传
...legend.
...奇
...Daddy.
传奇
American daddy.
这怎么回事吗
What the hell was that?
一个... 中国人
A... Chinese guy?
你好　我们要办个结婚证
Hi. Hello. Uh, we need a marriage license,
但我们想跳过等待期
but we need to skip the waiting period because...
我们深爱着对方
we're in love.
我将帮你们取消等待期
Aw. I'm gonna waive this waiting period right now.
真的?!
Oh, really?!
要是我能这么作 我肯定会
Is what I would say if I could waive the waiting period,
但遗憾的是只有法官才能
but unfortunately, only a judge can do that.
那我们能见法官吗
Oh. Well, so can we see a judge?
- 当然了 - 真的?!
- Absolutely. - Really?!
假如你们今天有机会可以见到的话 我当然会让你们见
Is what I would say if there was any chance of you seeing a judge today,
不过今天没机会
which there isn't.
你为什么老是耍我?!
Why are you doing this to us?!
因为正在拍录像!
'Cause you're on Candid Camera!
- 真的?! - 要是...
- Really?! - Is what I would say...
你知道吗? 我们知道了
You know what? We get it.
好　这是第二套方案
Okay, this is a good plan B.
法官是人 是人就要去厕所
Judges are people. People go to the batoom.
法官就必定要经过这里
A judge is bound to come by eventually,
然后我们就可以结婚了
and we'll get married.
我肯定我们不用等多久
I'm sure we won't be waiting long.
天那　我们就去 自动售货机才30秒钟
Geez, you go to a vending machine for 30 seconds.
一帮老家伙
Vultures.
什么?
What?
这里?
Here?
我们可以打发打发时间
Yeah. Got a little time to kill.
天哪　都是因为 这件衣服　对吧?
Oh, my God, it's the T-shirt, isn't it?
不是
No.
有点
A little.
今天你实在不对劲
Something is seriously wrong with you.
那是同不同意?
So what, is that a no?
- 行　我们干吧 - 好的
- All right, let's do it. - All right.
恩　那这个?
Um, also...?
- 是的　我不脱 - 太好了
- Yes, I'll leave it on. - Sweet.
哥们　我们放弃吧 这不可能发生了
Guys, let's bail. This is never gonna happen.
我知道现在事情有点糟糕
Look, I know this is turning into a bit of a disaster,
但是　相信 这比那个烂摊子要好
but believe me, it's better than the alternative.
你给你大学里 所有疯狂的单身朋友
You throwing a big, free party with lots of booze and food
开了个派对　那么多酒 东西都免费吃
and all your single, desperate girlfriends from college?
是的　很高兴 结果不是最糟的
Yeah,  glad we dodged that bullet.
法官 法官 快来　快来
Judge! Judge, come on. Come on, come on, come on!
- 关了它 - 好的
- Turn it off. - Okay.
我们可以今天结婚吗?
May we please get married today?
一般来说我会说不可以
Now, normally I would say no to a request like that,
但是你们两个让我印象深刻
but you two impress me.
你们两个在一起 同甘共苦过了十年
Just the fact that you've been together for ten years,
站在彼此的身边不离不弃
standing by each other's side through thick and thin,
从没动摇
never wavering.
- 那是什么? - 什么吗?
- What was that? - What was what?
你们的表情!是怎么回事?
That little look. What was that?
爱的表情
A look of love.
你们两个人一起同甘共苦?
You two have stood together through thick and thin, right?
- 你知道　什么胖　什么瘦? - 是　我意思　我都经历过
- You know, what's thick, what's thin? - Yeah, I mean, all... yeah.
我有...
I have.
那个表情到底是怎么回事?
All  right, what was that look?
怎么啦?
What's going on?
他们在夏天的时候曾经分手过
They broke up over the summer.
莉莉跑到了旧金山 这两个人刚刚在柜子里做爱
Lily totally ran off to San Francisco and these two just had sex in the closet.
什么? 在这 我们要宣誓诚实
What? We're under oath.
我们没有
No, we're not.
我们有必要诚实 他是个法官
Yeah, we are. He's a judge.
我们为什么要宣誓?
Wh-- did we take an oath?
你知道什么是宣誓
Do you even know what an oath is?
知道　法院
Uh, yeah. Courthouse.
宣誓　我们就在这下面
Oath. We're under it.
哥们　看来今天是不行了
Guys. It's looking like this isn't gonna happen.
不　马修　今天一定要结婚
No, Marshall, we are gonna get married today.
宝贝　无论去哪我们 都要拿到结婚证
Baby, anyplace we go, we're gonna need a marriage license.
除了国际公共水域
Except international waters.
所以　我们去找个船长
So-so let's find a ship captain.
船长能让我们结婚
A ship captain can marry us.
这地方船很多
There's boats all over this place.
那些垃圾堆里 不是浮着些木船吗
Oh, is that what those wooden things are floating between the garbage?
好主意　这能行 我们走吧
This is a great idea. This is gonna work. Let's go.
打扰了 你是船长吗
Excuse me. Are you a ship captain?
这是我的游戏机
This is my machine.
- 我去跟她谈谈 - 不　让我去
-  I should go talk to her. - No, let me.
- 我们去赌一把? - 好的
- Blackjack? - Yeah.
我找到了一个人 他说可以用他的船带我们出去
Well, I found a guy who said he'd be willing to put his boat in my slip,
所以我们又接近了点
so we're getting closer.
好　莉莉 今天结婚就那么重要吗
Okay, Lil, why is it so important to do this today?
因为　如果我们 今天不结婚的话
Because... if we don't do it today,
以后就要举办一个盛大的婚礼
I just know we're gonna wind up having a huge wedding
然后就会有一大群中西部来的人
with a huge crowd full of huge Midwestern people
一边喝着蛋黄酱
looking all disapproving and judging me
一边不屑的谈论我
while sipping little cups of mayonnaise
还有整晚都会 开我以前逃跑的玩笑
and-and cracking runaway bride jokes all night long.
- 没人会这样 - 是的　他们不会
- Nobody's gonna do that. - No, they're not
因为我不会 给他们这样的机会
because I'm not gonna give them the chance.
我要去找个船长　然后今晚就结婚
I'm gonna find a ship captain and we're gonna be married tonight.
宝贝　这太疯狂了
Sweetie, this is crazy.
你不可能找到船长的
You're never gonna find a ship capt...
莉莉　我们找到一个船长了
Hey, Lily. Found a ship captain.
- 什么 - 真的
- What? - Yeah.
第一个跟我们说话的人就是个船长
First guy we talked to. Ship captain.
要多巧有多巧
How great is that?
看到了吗?这就是命运
See? See, this is destiny.
船长　你能带我们到国际公共水域 并给我们证婚吗?
So, captain, can you take us out to international waters and marry us?
当然可以
I sure can.
如果要说两件我最喜欢做的事 就是给人们证婚
If there's two things I love, it's bringing people together in marriage
- 和挣5000美元 - 什么
- and making $5,000. - What?
5000美元　成交 我们接受了　各位 来吧
Deal. $5,000, okay, we can do that. Come on, everybody.
把你们的现金交拿出来 不要犹豫　行动吧
Fork over your cash. Don't think. Just do it.
我能帮你们弄到钱
I can get us that money.
怎么弄?
How?
今天你们有没有注意到
Have you noticed that all day today
那些中国人过来跟我打招呼
Chinese guys have been coming up and saying hi to me?
你有没有注意到 我没问你为什么
Yes. Have you noticed I haven't asked about it
因为我怕听到答案
because I'm too scared of the answer?
其实他们是我的赌友
Well, those are my old gambling buddies.
事实上　我曾经 一天到晚都在这呆着
Truth is... I used to come here all the time.
玩一个古老的中国玩法 "行还是不行"
Play an old Chinese game called "Shing Hasabu Shing".
然后出了点小问题
Had a small gambling problem.
事实上也不怎么小
Actually, it wasn't so small. I...
我输掉了我所有的积蓄
kind of lost my entire life's savings.
但今晚我觉得我运气很好
But tonight, I don't know, I'm feeling hot.
我想我能赢钱
I think I can win us that money.
不行　我不能 让你拿我们的钱赌
No, we're not letting you gamble all our money away.
如果你知道自己会赢 这就称不上赌了
Uh, it's not gambling if you absolutely know you're going to win.
我能赢到那笔
I'll get us that money.
我发誓...
I swear it, nay...
我宣誓
I oath it.
在那一晚之前我去很多赌场
Now, I had been to a lot of casinos before that night,
之后我也去过很多赌场
and I've been to a lot of casinos since,
但我从来没 见过象这样的赌法
but in all that time I've never seen a game quite like this one.
到现在  我都 不明白怎么玩的
To this day, I have no idea how it was played.
但幸运的是　巴尼懂
But luckily, Barney did.
你知道这怎么玩吗?
Do you understand what's happening?
毫无头绪.
Not a clue.
你觉得他是在赢吗
Do you think he's winning?
我根本不知道他是不是开始赌了
I don't even know if he's playing.
等等　我知道了 我知道怎么玩了
Wait, I get it. I understand this game.
你不知道
No, you don't.
西奥多 我完全知道怎么玩了
I totally understand the game, Theodore.
巴尼　把你的筹码都押上
Barney, split your tiles.
如果你能找到那个软心豆粒糖 就能赢三倍的钱
You can triple your money if you find the jellybean.
马修　别吵... 你以为我不知道自己在干什么吗...
Marshall, please. Don't you think I know what I'm...
天那　对啊
My God, you're right.
天那　太美了
Wow. It's beautiful.
谢谢　巴尼
Thanks, Barney.
你们看到了吗? 我今天手气太好了
Did you guys see me? I was on fire tonight.
我现在迫不及待想回去
Man, I can't wait to get back to the shore.
上帝　我爱赌博!
God, I love gambling!
回家以后我们得开个小会了
When we get home, we're gonna go to a little meeting. Okay?
为什么我就不能再玩一会?
Why can't I do it just a little?
好
Okay.
让我们开始吧
Let's get this started.
好...
Okay, uh...
你们想要严肃的 还是很有趣的?
you guys want the serious one or the funny one?
我想严肃的最好
Oh, I think... serious would be best.
你确定?那你就 听不到很多笑话了
You sure? I got a lot of great nautical jokes in there.
比如说你们如何浮起对方的船
Like how you two float each other's boat, stuff like that.
还是严肃的好
Yeah, serious is probably good.
我们今天在这里
"We stand witness today
来庆祝莉莉和马修的结合
"to celebrate the union of Lily and Marshall.
今天他们两人将合二为一
"Today, you two will become one,
共同分担生活中
"sharing your lives,
喜...怒...
"the happiness, the sadness,
哀...乐...
"the frustrations and the joy..."
这太棒了
This is pretty cool.
我不相信 你说绝不结婚
I can't believe you never want to get married.
我从没说"绝不"
I never said "never."
...来见证你们对彼此
"...to declare your love
爱和投入
"and devotion to each other
在你们家人和朋友
"in front of friends and family,
以及所以对你们来说 重要的人前面
"all the people who matter most to you."
怎么啦?
What was that?
什么怎么啦?
What was what?
那个表情 你们刚才 看了对方一眼
That little look. You two just shared a look.
- 我们不想结婚了 - 我们不结了
- We don't want to do this. - We don't.
你们开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding me?
你们第二次取消婚礼?
You guys are calling off another wedding?
在我花了所有钱 买了件伴娘的衣服之后?
After I spent all this money on a bridesmaid shirt?
我是不是跟谁赌他们会取消婚礼? 是吧? 我是跟谁赌的
Did I bet someone that they'd call it off? I did, didn't I? Who'd I bet?
你们还指望我们中有哪个人 会去参加你们第三次婚礼?
You actually expect any of us are gonna come to your third wedding?
当然了
Yes.
那一些会很棒
'Cause it's gonna be amazing.
以前我害怕面对马修的家人
Look, before I was afraid to face Marshall's family
而且我讨厌那些程序...
and-and I didn't want to do all that work, but...
现在我们到了这里
now that we're here...
我发现我必须要面对他的家人
I realize that I have to face Marshall's family
我发现我必须面对那些结婚的程序
and I really want to do all that work.
我也是
So do I.
虽然...我的家人 可能仍然生你的气
And yeah... my family might still be upset with you.
但他们看到我们在一起 他们将会知道到我们彼此有多相爱
But when they see us up there, they're gonna see how much we love each other.
没有什么事情会影响我们
And none of that other stuffs are gonna matter
我爱你 马修
I love you , Marshall
我也爱你 小百合
I love you too,Lily-pad
我现在宣布 你们成为丈夫和妻子
I now pronounce you man and wife.
- 什么?! - 什么?!
-What ?! -What ?!
怎么 我说错了吗?
Was that not right ?
我们结婚了?
Are...we married..?
你刚才宣布我们成婚了? 我们刚才讲那么多你都没听啊?
Did you just marry us..why don't you listening..
我们不想结婚了
We don't want to be married
我以为
Uh....I..surpose
我可以宣布婚姻无效
I could unpronounce you
-快点宣布无效 -快点宣布无效
-Unpronounce us -Unpronounce us
好的  我现在宣布婚姻无效
Okay, I unpronounce you man and wife
事情结束了
Ow, that was close.
这就是马修叔叔和莉莉阿姨的12秒婚姻
And that's the story how Uncle Marshall and Aunt Lily got married for 12 seconds
发生在靠近大西洋城某个地方的故事
somewhere off the coast of Atlantic City
泰德
Ted
Hey Guys
Hey....Ted
罗宾在这儿?
Is Robin here?
希望是...
Man, I hope so...